Guide to the William Hewlett Papers M1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Financial, 1945-2008
  - Subseries E: Trust Funds and Estate, 1958-2008
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 4 of 4), 1979 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 1 of 2), 1980 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 2 of 2), 1980 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 1 of 4), 1981 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 2 of 4), 1981 (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 3 of 4), 1981 (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 4 of 4), 1981 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General, 1982 (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General, 1983 (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General, 1984 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General, 1985 (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General, 1986 (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 1 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 2 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 317, Folder 5)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 3 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 4 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 317, Folder 7)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 1 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 2 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 3 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 1 of 2), 1990 (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 2 of 2), 1990 (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 1 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 2 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 3 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 1 of 2), 1991 (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General (part 2 of 2), 1991 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: General Information, 1977-1997 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Investments (part 1 of 2), 1977 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Investments (part 2 of 2), 1977 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Meetings, 1982 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Meetings, 1984 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Meetings, 1985-1992 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Paid Bills, 1991 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Reconciliation Reports (part 1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Reconciliation Reports (part 2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Records of Checks Drawn, 1977 (Flat-box 1)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Sale of Securities, Form 144, 1982 (Box 320, Folder 9)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Taxes (1980), 1980-1981 (Box 320, Folder 10)
    - Hewlett Children's Trusts: Wells Fargo Statements, 1978 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Hewlett Family Library: Repairs to Fire Damaged Books/Zukor Art Conservation, 2002-2003 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Hewlett Family Library: Robert Boehm Projects, 1996-2002 (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: Assets and Stock History, 1993-1998 (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: Federal Taxes (1996), 1996-1997 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: Payroll, 1996 (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: State Taxes (1996), 1995-1997 (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: Ward Creek Water Company (part 1 of 5), 1961, 1995-1999 (Box 321, Folder 8)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: Ward Creek Water Company (part 2 of 5), 1961, 1995-1999 (Box 321, Folder 9)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: Ward Creek Water Company (part 3 of 5), 1961, 1995-1999 (Box 321, Folder 10)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: Ward Creek Water Company (part 4 of 5), 1961, 1995-1999 (Box 321, Folder 11)
    - Hewlett Family Trust: Ward Creek Water Company (part 5 of 5), 1961, 1995-1999 (Box 321, Folder 12)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Accounting, 1997-1998 (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Adjusted Journal Entries, 1999 (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1979 (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1980 (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1981 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Alliance Holding, 1994 (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: AmeriGas Partners, 1998-1999 (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Bell Atlantic, 1999 (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Berkshire Hathaway, 1998-1999 (Box 322, Folder 9)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Buckeye Partners, 1998-2000 (Box 322, Folder 10)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Compaq Computer Corporation, 1998 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Duff and Phelps Utilities Income, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: El Paso Energy, 1998 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Harcourt General, 1998-2000 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Hawaiian Electric, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Heritage Cash Trust, 1999 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Kinder Morgan, 1998-2000 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Lucent Technologies, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 8)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Neiman Marcus, 1999 (Box 323, Folder 9)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Oracle, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 10)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Pacific Gas and Electric, 1999-2000 (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: PIMCO Advisors Holdings, 1998-2000 (Box 323, Folder 12)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Prentiss Properties Trust, 1998 (Box 323, Folder 13)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Red Brick, 1998 (Box 323, Folder 14)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: RFS Hotel Investors, 1998 (Box 323, Folder 15)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Rubbermaid, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 16)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Santa Fe Pacific Pipeline Partners, 1998 (Box 323, Folder 17)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Silicon Graphics, 2000 (Box 323, Folder 18)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Spieker Properties, 2000 (Box 323, Folder 19)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Stagecoach Funds, 1998 (Box 323, Folder 20)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: Texas Utilities, 1999-2000 (Box 323, Folder 21)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Assets: US Liquids, 1999 (Box 323, Folder 22)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Bank Statements, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General (part 1 of 8), 1977-1992, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General (part 2 of 8), 1977-1992, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General (part 3 of 8), 1977-1992, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General (part 4 of 8), 1977-1992, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General (part 5 of 8), 1977-1992, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General (part 6 of 8), 1977-1992, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General (part 7 of 8), 1977-1992, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General (part 8 of 8), 1977-1992, 1999 (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: General Ledger, 1999 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Merrill Lynch Account, 1998 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Raymond James and Associates Recommendations, 1998-1999 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Recommendations Made to Walter B. Hewlett, 1995 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Robert Thomas Securities Recommendations (part 1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - James S. Hewlett Trust: Robert Thomas Securities Recommendations (part 2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Lorreta M. Kopmeier Trust, 1985-1990 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Louise R. Hewlett Trust: General, 1966 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Louise R. Hewlett Trust: General, 1968 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Louise R. Hewlett Trust: General, 1969-1970 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Louise R. Hewlett Trust: General, 1977 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Louise R. Hewlett Trust: Termination and Distribution (part 1 of 4), 1963-1977 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Louise R. Hewlett Trust: Termination and Distribution (part 2 of 4), 1963-1977 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Louise R. Hewlett Trust: Termination and Distribution (part 3 of 4), 1963-1977 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Louise R. Hewlett Trust: Termination and Distribution (part 4 of 4), 1963-1977 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Agency Account, 1979-1980 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Agency Account, 1980 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Distributions, 1992-1993 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Distributions, 1994-1995 (Box 327, Folder 7)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Distributions, 1996 (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Fast-Tax Statements (part 1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 327, Folder 9)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Fast-Tax Statements (part 2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 327, Folder 10)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Fast-Tax Statements, 1993-1994 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Fast-Tax Statements, 1994 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Fast-Tax Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Fast-Tax Statements, 1996-1997 (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Financial Statements (1992-1995), 1994-1996 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Financial Statements (part 1 of 3), 1996 (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Financial Statements (part 2 of 3), 1996 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Financial Statements (part 3 of 3), 1996 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: General, 1977 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: General, 1978 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: General (part 1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 329, Folder 5)
      Oversize material was separated and moved to Flat Box 1.
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: General (part 2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Paid Bills, 1992-1993 (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Paid Bills, 1993-1994 (Box 329, Folder 8)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Paid Bills, 1995 (Box 329, Folder 9)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Paid Bills, 1996-1997 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Stocks Sold, 1993-1994 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Stocks Sold, 1995 (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Stocks Sold, 1996 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Taxes (1991), 1991-1992 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Taxes (1992 and 1993), 1992-1994 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Taxes (1994), 1994-1995 (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Taxes (1995), 1995-1996 (Box 330, Folder 8)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Taxes (1996), 1996-1997 (Box 330, Folder 9)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 1 of 3), 1992 (Box 330, Folder 10)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 2 of 3), 1992 (Box 330, Folder 11)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 3 of 3), 1992 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 1 of 3), 1993-1994 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 2 of 3), 1993-1994 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 3 of 3), 1993-1994 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 1 of 5), 1994 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 2 of 5), 1994 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 3 of 5), 1994 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 4 of 5), 1994 (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 5 of 5), 1994 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 1 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 2 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 3 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Trial Balance (part 4 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Wells Fargo Asset Statements, 1992 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Wells Fargo Asset Statements, 1993 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Wells Fargo Cash Statements, 1992 (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Wells Fargo Cash Statements, 1993 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Wells Fargo Cash Statements, 1994 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Wells Fargo Cash Statements, 1995 (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Wells Fargo Cash/Asset Statements, 1994 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Mary H. Jaffe Trust: Wells Fargo Cash/Asset Summary Statements, 1996 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Bancroft Library, 1979-1982 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Carnegie Institution, 1981-1985 (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1986 (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Colorado College, 1985 (Box 333, Folder 11)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Financial Transactions, 1981-1991 (Box 333, Folder 12)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, General, 1981-1990 (Box 333, Folder 13)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Kenyon College, 1986 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Legal History, 1980-1985 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Marquette University, 1981-1986 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Menlo School and College, 1982-1988 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Mills College, 1985-1987 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Monterey Institute for Research in Astronomy, 1984 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Newcastle University, 1984-1985 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Research Corporation, 1983-1986 (Box 334, Folder 8)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Smith College, 1987-1988 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Technology Center of Silicon Valley, 1988 (Box 334, Folder 10)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, University of Santa Clara, 1981-1982 (Box 334, Folder 11)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Files from Roger W. Heyns, Yale University, 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 12)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Requests and Responses, 1983 (Box 334, Folder 13)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Requests and Responses, 1984 (Box 334, Folder 14)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Requests and Responses, 1985 (Box 334, Folder 15)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Requests and Responses, 1986 (Box 334, Folder 16)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Requests and Responses, 1987 (Box 334, Folder 17)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Requests and Responses, 1988 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Tax Returns (part 1 of 8), 1980-1992 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Tax Returns (part 2 of 8), 1980-1992 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Tax Returns (part 3 of 8), 1980-1992 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Tax Returns (part 4 of 8), 1980-1992 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Tax Returns (part 5 of 8), 1980-1992 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Tax Returns (part 6 of 8), 1980-1992 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Tax Returns (part 7 of 8), 1980-1992 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Tax Returns (part 8 of 8), 1980-1992 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Wells Fargo Statements, 1981-1983 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Wells Fargo Statements, 1984-1985 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Wells Fargo Statements, 1986-1987 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Penta Corporation Charitable Trust: Wells Fargo Statements, 1988-1991 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Rosemary B. Hewlett Estate: Planning Living Trust, 1978-1979 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Rosemary B. Hewlett Trust: Whelan and Gratny Capital Management: JP Morgan Statements, 1999-2000 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Walter B. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Walter B. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1980-1981 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Walter B. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1981 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Walter B. Hewlett Trust: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Walter B. Hewlett Trust: General, 1977 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Walter B. Hewlett Trust: General, 1977-1978 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1977 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1977-1978 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1980 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Agency Account, 1981 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 1 of 4), 1977-1999 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 2 of 4), 1977-1999 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 3 of 4), 1977-1999 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 4 of 4), 1977-1999 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 1 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 2 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 3 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 4 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 5 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 6 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 7 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 8 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: General (part 9 of 9), 1987-1990 (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Stocks and Bonds Sold (part 1 of 3), 1981-1994 (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Stocks and Bonds Sold (part 2 of 3), 1981-1994 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Stocks and Bonds Sold (part 3 of 3), 1981-1994 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Tax Return and Working Papers, 1988-1989 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - William A. Hewlett Trust: Trust Meeting (July 18), 1989 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - William R. and Rosemary B. Hewlett Community Property Account, 1996 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only (part 1 of 5), 2000-2001 (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only (part 2 of 5), 2000-2001 (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only (part 3 of 5), 2000-2001 (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only (part 4 of 5), 2000-2001 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only (part 5 of 5), 2000-2001 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only, 2001 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only (part 1 of 2), 2002 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only (part 2 of 2), 2002 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only: Mike Roosevelt Invoices, 2001-2003 (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: 720 Los Trancos Road: Paid Bills: Fire Related Only: Ted Carlstrom Invoices, 2002 (Box 342, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Accounts Receivable, 2001 (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Bank Statements, 2004-2005 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Bank Statements, 2006-2007 (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Bank Statements Investments, 2005-2006 (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 1 December, 2000 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 2 January, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 3 February, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 4 March, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 5 April, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 6 May, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 7 June, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 10)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 8 July, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 11)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 9 August, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 10 September, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 11 October, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 12 November, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 13 December, 2001-2002 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 14 January, 2002 (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 15 February, 2002 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 16 March, 2002 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Administrative Trust: Chubb Worksheet # 17 April, 2002 (Box 344, Folder 9)